Jessie Lloyd O'Connor Papers, 1850-1988
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- SERIES III. WRITINGS 1889-1989, 9 linear ft.
  Notes and research material is a large subseries consisting of the many notes Jessie wrote and compiled throughout her life. These contain her thoughts on many subjects, ranging from story ideas, names and phone numbers of those she sought to enlist in her causes, or commentary on contemporary events. Where possible the notes have been arranged by date or subject. The final writings subseries is material written by Other family members. Particularly interesting are the writings of her pacifist mother Lola Maverick Lloyd.
- SERIES IV. ORGANIZATION FILES 1918-1988, 12.75 linear ft.
  Alphabetically arranged files.
  This series consists of files on organizations in which O'Connor was deeply involved, such as the League of Women Shoppers, as well as others with which she seems to have had a more passing connection, making donations and/or collecting mailings. The series includes correspondence, brochures and other printed material, newsletters, and notes. O'Connor worked in the leadership of a number of local organizations-the American League against War and Fascism in Pittsburgh; the Progressive Party, especially Henry Wallace's presidential campaign, and the CIO- Political Action Committee in Texas; and in Chicago for Hull House (where she was a resident in the early 1940s), The Metropolitan Housing and Planning Council, and the Women's International League for Peace and Freedom, among others. Files for these organizations document O'Connor's extensive volunteer work and more generally, organizations of the American Left, especially in the Cold War years. The papers also contain material from organizations with which she appears to have had no direct involvement. These have been saved to highlight the variety of her interests and to suggest the wide array of progressive and radical organizations that existed during the 1930s through the Cold War years, as well as those from the 1960s on which may be more familiar.
  Some of the more ephemeral organizational materials have been grouped with other material in the appropriate category in SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES.
- SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES 1893-1988, 4.4 linear ft.
  Arranged alphabetically.
  The subject files contain a wide variety of printed material, as well as correspondence, notes, and some organizational materials. Broad subject areas that are also represented by material in the WRITINGS and ORGANIZATION FILES series, such as labor and peace, tend to contain miscellaneous printed material, often from organizations with which O'Connor seemed to have little or peripheral involvement. Other broad areas of interest, such as Music and Children/youth document her deep interest in subjects near to her heart, respectively songwriting and folk dancing, and her two children. Files on admired friends and activists like Ella Reeve Bloor, Anne and Carl Braden, and Pete Seeger, also contain material of a more personal nature. Some of the documents filed here may have been research material for O'Connor's writings or potential writings that were not identified as such and thus may overlap with materials in the WRITINGS series.
- SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIAL 1850s-1988
  - Articles and interviews
    - Articles about1929-89 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      [see also SERIES III. WRITINGS-Federated Press--Harlan, KY, and oversize material]
    - Interviews
      - Smith Centennial Study (Jacqueline Van Voris): correspondence and transcript1971-75 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Studs Terkel: cassette tape (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Ann West: transcript1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Personal records
    - Address and birthday booksundated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Card file of addresses for individuals and organizationsundated (Box 1)
    - Health/medical: correspondence, notes, dental x-rays, and measurements1922-88, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Marriage announcement1930 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Papers: Tina Simmons' notes and correspondence re: organization of JLO papers1977-78, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
      [see also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE-Friends and associates-Simmons, Christina]
    - Passports, visas, certificates of vaccination, and drivers licenses1926-70 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Education
    [see also oversize material for diplomas]
    - Grade school
      - Papers, assignments, and artworkcirca 1912-16 (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - Report cards and memorabilia1914-15, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Church school: report card, diplomas, and projects1915-16, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - New Trier High School, Winnetka, IL
      - Notes and papers1918, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Report cards1916-20 (Box 2, Folder 9)
      - Memorabilia1921, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Alumni Association: correspondence and 1970 reunion materials1921, 1923, 1970-76 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Smith College
      - Miscellaneous class notes1925, undated (Box 3, Folder 3-8)
      - Miscellaneous class notes1925, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
      - Class papers and exams, 1921-25, undated
        - Economics 21-38 (Box 4, Folder 2)
        - English 11-313 (Box 4, Folder 3-5)
        - History 11, 33, 34, 331b (Box 4, Folder 6)
        - Philosophy 21b, 32a (Box 4, Folder 7)
        - Statistics (Box 4, Folder 8)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Extracurricular activities: Smith College Monthly articles, notes for articles [SCM or Press Board?], and Italian Club meeting notes1924-25, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Grade reports1921-25 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Memorabilia
        - Notes from friendsundated (Box 4, Folder 12)
        - Miscellaneous1921-25 (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Alumnae activities
        - Correspondence1928-84 (Box 5, Folder 1)
        - 1955 reunion report: notes, drafts, and galley proof (Box 5, Folder 2)
        - Biographical questionnaire (completed) and miscellaneous printed material1956-75, undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Financial and legal material
    - Birth certificate1904 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Expenses and income
      - Bank statements and check stubs1916, 1922-45 (Box 6, Folder 2-17)
      - Bank statements1945-56, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 1-12)
      - Notebook1933-35, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Taxes1937-59, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 2-3)
    - Insurance1949-51 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Trusts and estates: correspondence and legal documents
      - Edith Wynner Trust1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
      - George Maverick Estate and Maverick Properties1944-57, 1975-77 (Box 8, Folder 6)
        [see also Homes and other real estate-Maverick ranch, TX, and SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE-Family-Green, George]
      - Jessie Lloyd O'Connor Trust1964-76 (Box 8, Folder 7)
        [see also Wills]
      - John Bross Lloyd Trust1947-69 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - Lola Maverick Lloyd Estate1945-47 (Box 8, Folder 9)
      - Madge Bird Lloyd Trust1930-72 (Box 8, Folder 10)
      - Mary Maverick Lloyd Estate1976 (Box 8, Folder 11)
      - Northern Trust Company1945-83 (Box 8, Folder 12)
      - William Bross Lloyd (The Lloyd Properties) (Box 8)
        [see also SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE-Friends and associates-Johansen, Agnes; O'Flaherty, Frances]
      - Christmas Trust1935-48 (Box 8, Folder 13)
      - Correspondence1919-51, 1984, undated (Box 8a, Folder 1-5)
      - Court documents1951 (Box 9, Folder 1)
      - Permanent Family Fund1940-49 (Box 9, Folder 2)
      - Testamentary Trust and Report of Examination1955, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous financial1935-70 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Wills1970-81 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Harvey O'Connor/Blanche J. O'Connor divorce1930-31 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous contracts, correspondence, and legal documents1947-83 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Death
    - Obituaries1988-89 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Memorial service21 Jan 1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Condolence letters and devotionals1988, undated (Box 9, Folder 10-12)
  - F.B.I. files1941-72 (part 1 and 2) (Box 9, Folder 9a-9b)
  - Homes and other real estate
    [see oversize material for blueprints and maps]
    - Jamaica, W.I. (Bu Saaba): correspondence
      [see also SERIES II CORRESPONDENCE-Friends and associates-Laning, Claire; and Neil, Rebecca]
      - James Crearer1946-52 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Miscellaneous1943-86 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Maverick ranch, TX
      [see also Financial and legal material-Trusts and estates-George Maverick Estate and Maverick Properties, and SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE-Family-Green, George]
      - General1973, 1978, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Reece and Ellen Whiting1948-85, undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Warrens Point, Little Compton; and Sakonnet, RI
      - General: correspondence, articles, floor plan, records, and deeds1946-88, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Volya (yacht)
        - 1936-50, undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
        - 1951-70, undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Watch House1959-79, undated (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Winnetka, IL.: correspondence, house records, articles, and reports re: historic preservation1946-47, 1961-77, undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous1941-81, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Memorabilia
    [see also oversize material]
    - Artwork1926, 1936, undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Greeting cards and postcardscirca 1910-60s
      - Christmas and miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Valentines/birthday (Box 11, Folder 7-8)
    - Poems and songs by others about Jessie and Harvey1936-85, undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous: invitations, awards, library and membership cards, Christmas cards, menus, plays, programs, artwork, lists, JLO's braids, and printed material1919-83 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Family
    - Beshears, Georgia Lloyd Berndt and Bob Beshears (sister and brother-in-law)1937-88, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Bross-Lloyd-Demarest genealogyundated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Bross, William1949, 1977, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Demarest Family1939-60 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Green, Mary Vance1950-87 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Green, Rena Maverick1954-68 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Green, Robert B.1962 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Horwitz, Lola Lloyd1958, 1962, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Keller, Deborah Maverick Kelley1986-88 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Kelley, Augusta Maverick1954, 1985, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Kelley, Augustus M.1951-early 1960s (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Kelley, Florence M.1960 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Kelley, Nicholas1965, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Kelley, Nicholas, Jr. 1956 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Lloyd Family
      - General1954-88, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Miscellaneous individuals1972-88, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Lloyd, David Demarest1950-63 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Lloyd, Demarest1932, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Lloyd, Henry Demarest
      - General correspondence and articles1903-86, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - "Biographical Notes on the Life of Henry Demarest Lloyd" by Caroline Lloyd Strobell1902, 1938-40, undated (includes letter from Ella Reeve Bloor, 1938) (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence re: Wealth vs. Commonwealth1936-37, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Lloyd, Henry Demarest, Jr.1951-52, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Lloyd, Jessie Bross (grandmother)1897-1905, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Lloyd, John Bird (brother)1931-60, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Lloyd, John Bross1957, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Lloyd, Lola Maverick
      - Correspondence1944-48, 1962 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Articles and reminiscences1945-86, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Divorce1916 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Death
        - Correspondence1944-45, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
        - Obituaries and memorial service1944 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Lloyd, Mary Maverick (sister): Obituaries and condolence letters1976 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Lloyd, Mary Norris (sister-in-law)1962, 1972, undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Lloyd, Robin1944, 1974, 1980, 1988, undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Lloyd, William Bross, Sr. (father)1918-88 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Lloyd, William Bross, Jr. (brother)1942-84, undated (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Maverick Family
      - General: correspondence, articles, pamphlets, lists, and memorabilia1889, 1934-85, undated (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous individuals1952-87, undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Maverick, Jim and Hazel1969, 1987, undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Maverick, Maury1936-68, undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Maverick, Maury, Jr.1959-80 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Maverick, Samuel1936-85, undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - O'Connor Family: miscellaneous memorabilia1942-70, undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - O'Connor, Harvey
      - Articles and other printed material1933-87, undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Health: correspondence and notes1952-86, undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Memorabilia: award, notes, poems, and drawingcirca 1945-88, undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - O'Connor children
      - General1950, 1980, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Kathleen1943-57, undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Stephen1943-89, undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Strobell, Caroline Lloyd1939-40, undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Photographs
    - Jessie Lloyd O'Connor
      - Alonecirca 1916-84, undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - With others1910s-84, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - O'Connor family groups1940s-64, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - O'Connor, Harvey1930s?-1983, undated (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - O'Connor, Kathleen1950s-60s, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - O'Connor, Stephen1940s-60s, undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Beshears, Georgia Lloyd Berndt and family1940s (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Lloyd family
    - Family groups (includes Lola Maverick Lloyd, William Bross Lloyd, Sr., and their children; and Jessie Bross Lloyd with Henry Demarest Lloyd as a child)1904-55, undated (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Photograph album (includes Ford Peace Ship Expedition, 1915)circa 1915-18 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Lloyd, Lola Maverickcirca 1916-43, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Lloyd, Mary Maverickundated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Lloyd, William Bross, Sr.undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Lloyd, William Bross, Jr. and Mary Norris Lloyd and family1916-71, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Maverick/Green families1850s-1910s, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Friends and associates
    - A-R (includes Emily Balch, Pat Cush, Hays Jones, Earl Robinson) (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - S-W (includes Rosika Schwimmer, Sula Serafini, Ching-ling Soong, Caroline Bedell Thomas, and Edith Wynner) (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Individuals and groups, unidentified1910s-79, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Sites, scenes, and subjects
    - Homes and Volya (yacht)1916-44, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - [New Zealand1899, possibly for a book?] (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - [European trip1926 ?] (includes photo album) (Box 16, Folder 1)
      [see also oversize material for another photo album]
    - Soviet Unioncirca 1926-27 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Trip to Cuba, Jamaica, and Yucatan (also includes a few family photos)1931: photo album (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Miner's and steel companies strike, Pittsburgh1933 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      [see also SERIES III. WRITINGS-Federated Press-Pennsylvania-Pittsburgh]
    - Marion, North Carolina mill-workers1930s (Box 16, Folder 5)
      [see also SERIES III. WRITINGS-Federated Press-North and South Carolina]
    - Miscellaneous1916-72, undated (Box 6)
- SERIES II. CORRESPONDENCE 1875-1988
  - Family
    - Berndt, Anne and Arthur (nephew)1947-86, undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Berndt, Lola (niece)1952-71 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Beshears, Georgia Lloyd Berndt (sister) (includes first husband Paul Berndt and second husband Bob Beshears)
      - 1918-52 (Box 17, Folder 3-8)
      - 1953-69 (Box 18, Folder 1-7)
      - 1970-88, undated (Box 19, Folder 1-5)
    - Cribbs, Karen1976-86 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Dillon, Rowena McNeel1960?, 1963 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Drummey, Lloyd (Del)1980 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Fenstermaker, Bebe1957-88, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Fenstermaker, Martha1963-86 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Fenstermaker, Mary Rowena (Sissy)1963-88, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Fox, Jessie O'Connor (Harvey's sister) and Wayne
      - 1931-49 (Box 19, Folder 12-13)
      - 1950-71, undated (Box 20, Folder 1-4)
    - Goodrich, Clare1960, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Goodrich, Constance1962-65, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Goodrich, David1973 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Goodrich, Edith Maverick and Lloyd1952-84 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Goodrich, Madeleine Lloyd (great aunt)1940-58 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Gordon, Noel McNeel1954-66, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Gower, Martha Maverick Weise (cousin?)1954-88 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Green, George "Brother" (cousin)1921-77, undated [4 f] (Box 21, Folder 1-4)
      [see also SERIES I. BIOGRAPHICAL MATERIAL--Financial and legal material--Trusts and estates--George Maverick Estate and Maverick Properties, and Homes and other real estate-Maverick ranch, TX]
    - Green, Mary V. (cousin)1910-86, undated [2 f] (Box 21, Folder 5-6)
    - Green, Rena Maverick (aunt)1910-88, undated [2 f] (Box 21, Folder 7-8)
    - Green, Rowena Fenstermaker1918-88, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Green, Theodore Francis1950-59 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Greene, Alice Lloyd (cousin)1952-88 (Box 22, Folder 4-5)
    - Greene, David Lloyd and Janet1968-82 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Greene, Donald1970-76 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Hackett, Frances Goodrich1966-74 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Harrington, Linda Lloydcirca 1968-71 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Horwitz, Donald and Lola Lloyd (niece)1947-87, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Keller, Jane McNeel1960-86, undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Kelley, Augusta Maverick (aunt) and Nicholas
      - 1910-49 (Box 22, Folder 12)
      - 1950-84, undated (Box 23, Folder 1-2)
    - Kelley, Augustus and Nancy1948-59 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Kelley, Debby1981-86 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Kelley, Eva1963-88, undated (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Kelley, Florence M.1962-84 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Kelley, John Bertram and Hazel1944-70 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Kelley, Nick and Maggieundated (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Lane, Mary McNeel1975-85 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Lee, Nicole Berndt1975, undated (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Lloyd, Andrea Mathews1957-61 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Lloyd, Caroline (aunt)1944-64, undated (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Lloyd, Christopher and Jane1950-85, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Lloyd, David Demarest and Charlotte1941-67 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Lloyd, Demarest (Uncle Demi)1928-36 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Lloyd, Dorothy1920, 1953? (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Lloyd, Hal and Elizabeth1924-25, 1949, undated (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Lloyd, Henry Demarest, Jr.1922, 1955, undated (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Lloyd, Isabelle and Carrington1966-69 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Lloyd, Jessie Bross (grandmother)1888-1904 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Lloyd, John Bird, Sr.(half-brother), and Paulette1921-86, undated (Box 23, Folder 21-22)
    - Lloyd, John Bross (uncle)1924-59, undated (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Lloyd, Katharine (aunt)1944-78, undated (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Lloyd, Lola Maverick (mother)
      - 1903-25 (Box 24, Folder 3-8)
      - 1926-45 (Box 25, Folder 1-8)
      - undated (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Lloyd, Madge Bird (step-mother)circa 1920-71, undated (Box 26, Folder 2-4)
    - Lloyd, Mary Maverick (sister)
      - 1916-44 (Box 26, Folder 5-7)
      - 1945-59 (Box 27, Folder 1-6)
      - 1960-76, undated (Box 28, Folder 1-4)
    - Lloyd, Philip1968-85 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Lloyd, Robin (niece)1949-89, undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Lloyd, William Bross, Sr. (father)
      - 1904-21 (Box 28, Folder 7-8)
      - 1922-32 (Box 29, Folder 1-6)
      - 1933-41 (Box 30, Folder 1-)
      - 1942-46, undated (Box 31, Folder 1-6)
    - Lloyd, William, Jr. (brother) and Mary Norris
      - 1918-59 (Box 32, Folder 1-8)
      - 1960-88, undated (Box 33, Folder 1-6)
    - Lloyd, William III and Miriam1944-64 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Lloyd family (miscellaneous)1959-74, undated (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Maverick, Andrew (cousin?) and Emily1947-88, undated (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Maverick, Dorothy1945 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Maverick, Fontaine1975 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Maverick, Frank1983-85 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Maverick, George (uncle?) and Ruth1949-70 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Maverick, Jim and Hazel1937-83 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Maverick, Lewis (uncle) and Pirie1916-49 (Box 34, Folder 5-6)
    - Maverick, Lucy (aunt)1929-70 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Maverick, Mary Vance (grandmother)1906-25 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Maverick, Maury (cousin)1932-38 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Maverick, Maury, Jr.1967-88 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Maverick, Mitsou1968-88 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Maverick family (miscellaneous)1906-85 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - McCue, Ida (Aunt Bunny)1918-68, undated (Box 34, Folder 13-14)
    - McNeel, Paul and Jess (cousin?)1930-87, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Migdal-Lloyd, Lenore1986-88 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - O'Connor, Adrienne (granddaughter)1983-89, undated (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - O'Connor, Christiana (granddaughter)1969-88, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - O'Connor, Daniel (grandson)1981-82 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - O'Connor, Harvey1917-81, undated (Box 35, Folder 6-12)
    - O'Connor, Kathleen (daughter)1944-59 (Box 36, Folder 1-3)
    - O'Connor, Stephen, (son) Sherry Lukens Mazer (first wife), and Lucy (second wife)circa 1943-79, undated (Box 36, Folder 4-6)
    - O'Connor children (both)1950-58 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Perkins, Anne1962-88 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Perkins, Connie1956-70 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Perkins, Jim1987-88 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Perkins (miscellaneous)1969, undated (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Peterson, Amy Lloyd1967-68 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Ride, Gladys Evans (Harvey's cousin) and Tom1942-71, undated (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Strobell, Caroline Lloyd (Aunt Caro)circa 1918-40, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Taddei, M.L.1978 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Taylor, Harris (aunt)1948-65 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Weise, Anne (Maverick?) and Marty1950-88, undated (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Whittington, Anne1921, undated (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Unidentified or multiple family1932-87, undated (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Third party (family to and from friends and associates)
      - Beshears, Georgia Lloyd Berndt
        - 1923-49 (Box 37, Folder 11-13)
        - 1950-88, undated (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
      - Fox, Jessie1965-66 (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Lloyd, Henry Demarest1875, 1895, 1902 (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Lloyd, Lola Maverick1915-44 (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Lloyd, Mary Maverick
        - 1917-33 (Box 38, Folder 6-9)
        - 1934-74, undated (Box 39, Folder 1-7)
      - Lloyd, William Bross, Sr.circa 1904-45, undated (Box 39, Folder 8-9)
      - Lloyd, William Bross, Jr.1937-84, undated (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Maverick, Lucy1911-66? (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Maverick, Rena1942-45, undated (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - O'Connor, Harvey1929-83 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - O'Connor, Kathleen1949-85, undated (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - O'Connor, Stephen1950-87, undated (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous (Lloyd-McGarraugh)1938-68, undated (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Friends and associates
    - Addams, Jane1930, 1932 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Adler, Erni (Box 40)
      [see SERIES V. SUBJECT FILES-Political prisoners and refugees--Boschan, Paul]
    - Akin, Bette and Morris1959-85 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Alcala, Mary Mosquera1960-62 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Aldrich, Amey1930, 1953-63 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Allan, Seema and Bill1938-88, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Allen, Ben1952 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Allen, Jay and Ruth1951-52, 1985, 1986, undated (Box 40, Folder 14)